Trick or Treat my oh my what stupid
costumes you kids have why don't you all
come inside and enjoy some delicious
popcorn balls um my parents tell me not
to go into strangers houses
don't you worry nothing I'm friends with
your parents get inside my house grab
some of these delicious balls stay a
while do you have any candy I might have
some sweets inside how about y'all we'll
come inside and help me look yo guys I
think I hear my mom calling I think
you're right Brad maybe we should get
going so your name is Brad duh that's a
cute name you know I have a son about
your age his name is Brad too
why don't you come inside to meet him
I'm sure the two of you would be great
pals oh well um we really need to get
point
dude come on let's get going